[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This popular African-American group was founded in 1954. Its original members -- OKelly, Rudolph, Ronald and Vernon were from Cincinnati, Ohio.", "correct_answer": "The Isley Brothers", "incorrect_answers": ["The Allman Brothers", "The Walers", "The Who"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "TV fans know her best as Mrs. Edna Garret from The Facts of Life but she also played Cousin Claire in Rabbit Test.", "correct_answer": "Charlote Rae", "incorrect_answers": ["Valerie Curtin", "Shelly Morrison", "Imogene Coca"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Fletchs favorite team in the movie Fletch?", "correct_answer": "L.A. Lakers", "incorrect_answers": ["Boston Celtics", "Boston Celtics", "New York Knicks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do the beetles from the genus Nicrophorus do after finding a carcass?", "correct_answer": "They bury it.", "incorrect_answers": ["They remain right next to it and protect it violently.", "They wait for it to decompose.", "They tear it into small pieces."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Find the next number in this sequence: 8, 5, 4, 9, 1, 7, ...", "correct_answer": "6", "incorrect_answers": ["0", "3", "2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In algebra, what is an Abelian group?", "correct_answer": "A group that is commutative", "incorrect_answers": ["A group that is distributive", "A group that is reflexive", "A group that is transitive"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 64 AD there were terrible fires in Rome. Which Roman Emperor was busy playing his fiddle while the fires were burning?", "correct_answer": "None of the Emperors", "incorrect_answers": ["Caligula", "Nero", "Vespasian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Benjamin Martin use to stab Tavingtons horse in the film The Patriot?", "correct_answer": "The American Flag", "incorrect_answers": ["A knife", "A bayonet", "An axe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What emotional state does the gesture of narrowed eyes convey?", "correct_answer": "Threat, distrust", "incorrect_answers": ["Satisfaction, joy", "Sadness, frustration", "Anger, excitement"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does an average single fetus acquire at the age of three months?", "correct_answer": "fingerprints", "incorrect_answers": ["hair", "earlobes", "feet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Cpl. Hicks first name in the movie Aliens?", "correct_answer": "Dwayne", "incorrect_answers": ["Derek", "John", "Dwight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the Christian  tradition there are 39 books in the Old Testament. How many books are there in the Old Testament according to the Jewish tradition?", "correct_answer": "24", "incorrect_answers": ["39", "5", "65"]}]